Justin Brueske

17875 126th St SE Becker, MN 55308 (763) 923-3848 justin.brueske@gmail.com

Justin has been with Canadian Pacific Railway for the past 14 years. During that time he has worked in the yard inspecting trains, on a rip tack repairing railcars, and on road truck repairing railcars on the line of road. For the past 5 years he has been at Shoreham repairing railcars and completing his own AAR billing. Justin has excellent troubleshooting skills and graduated with distinguished honor graduate from the 35M Field Artillery Radar course.

Experience

February 2023 - Present

Network Center Inc - Web Developer I

Building websites

August 2008 - January 2023

Canadian Pacific Railway - Crane/RoadTruck Carmen

- Inspection and repair of railcars.
- Completing FRA and AAR paperwork.
- Using various types of heavy equipment.

April 1999 - April 2008

Army National Guard, Anoka MN - 35M Radar Repair Technician

• Maintain and repair Q36 and Q37 Radar systems.

Education

September 2002 - May 2005

NEI Center at Dunwoody, Minneapolis, MN - AAS Degree in Computer Networking

Degree focused on hardware, software, networking and connectivity in terms of install/setup, maintenance, and troubleshooting in all areas.

Awards and Skills

- Distinguished Honor Graduate 35M Radar Repair Training
- Class A Driver's License
- Excellent troubleshooting skills